[{"answer": "Well, Piers, first of all, thank your brother for his service and we appreciate what he's doing.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "It may be targeted but not a chemical weapons depots, but maybe a military target may already be moving and what's the end game from a military point of view, how do you assess this?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "That's all pretty hard to say whether the United States will wait for Britain or not.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "And Christiane, in terms of the timing of any strike, are there any seen development today in Britain who's always been a key ally course to the Americans on issues like this and military actions like this where David Cameron the Prime Minister was staring defeat in the face on a vote on this and is now going for a second vote next Tuesday, does that mean we are unlikely to see any action even from the United States before that vote is taken place?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Well, partially, I'm happy that he is receiving the death sentence.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Are you happy with what has happened?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Well, no, because when you look at it, I mean, even though he wanted to be put to death, he want to be death in the blaze of glory in battle.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Is it not a better punishment perhaps that he does sit there thinking about what he did for the rest of his natural life?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Well, it was shocking and actually one of the safest places where you can be in our country is on a military base.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "What was the moment like for you when you turned and realized this man that you thought you knew so well had turned rouge enemy?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "One of the most important was is post-traumatic stress disorder.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "What are the long-standing injuries that you've suffered from this?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "Well, my kids cannot come up behind me and just say, \"Dad, I love you,\" without announcing themselves.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "In what way?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Absolutely because there were other signs they were prevalent with major signs activity while he was stationed at Walter Reed, but there are again because he was the first man, an Easterner to go though their program it was kind of like a hands-off approach.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "They should have identified the threat from Hasan earlier?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Well, he's a failure.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "It must have been a relief to you but what are your feelings to him as a human being to human being?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "It was a great day.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "Barack Obama, President of United States speaking on the 50th anniversary, what more do you need to see that equality and civil rights have marched to Washington and America?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "That's a question you'd have to ask him.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Why do you think President Obama is weary of going there?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "No doubt about it.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Would he not have understood that it's incumbent on any American president, any world leader of a decent civilized country to at least care enough to want to try and do something to prevent more of that happening?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Denial is not just a river in Egypt, I guess.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Star Jones what do you make here of what she had to say?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "... and twerking.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Again?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "First of all that's an impolite question, because a grown adult women should to be twerking unless she is dancing in the bush in Africa or performing on a stage like she's Beyonce.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "First of all can you twerk or not, Star?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "You know, it was fun for adults and if it's an all-adult venue with all-adults watching, then, hey, bonus, you know.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Why do you feel so enraged by what I thought is a bit of fun from Miley Cyrus?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "Shouldn't you, as a responsible parent, stop your children watching this if you felt so delicate about it?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "That's a good point, that's a good point.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "What's the fan base of One Direction, its girls 8 to 14 or 15?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "The point of -- the problem is that parents have started to allow, or have, for several years now, allowed televisions, celebrities, reality stars, to be the influencers in their children's lives.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "And I say, why, why can't she grow up and be a bit naughty like Lady Gaga, like Rihanna, who we revere and say are so wonderfully expressive and creative?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "We're having the big 95th birthday party on Saturday for 200 people.", "docId": "130828pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "I want to wish Grandma Pauline (ph) a very happy 95th birthday on -- when is it, what day?", "qSentId": 445}]